New Zealand
Marist College
New Zealand
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.1.6
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass Plate Negatives; New Zealand
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Material, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Indexed Photogrpahs, 2.1.1.2.1
            - New Zealand, 2.1.1.2.1.6
                - Wellington panorama from hill overlooking center of the city, big bare space in foreground, 1921; 10 (Box 1272)
                5x7
                - Wellington panorama from hill overlooking center of city, big bare space in foreground (more distant view of 5-50), 1921; 11
                - Wellington, view taken from hill just above tram line, 1921; 12
                - Suburb of Wellington on shore of Cook Strait, Lowell Thomas on cannon in foreground, 1921; 13
                - Wellington, view taken from hill just above tram line (similar to 5-52, showing less of city and more flowers in foreground), 1921; 14
                - Wellington from hill near tea kiosk, 1921; 15
                - Panorama of fern palms, Auckland, 1921; 16
                - Panorama of fern palms, Auckland (same as 5-56, view from upon high bridge), 1921; 17
                - Tree ferns surrounded by thick jungle, 1921; 18
                - Tree fern, two slim tree trunks on left, 1921; 19
                - Close-up of branches of large tree fern, 1921; 20
                - Large bridge, 1921; 21
                - Three-coned volcano, 1921; 22
                - Entrance of model Maori village, “Dangerous” sign posted on totem, woman in foreground, 1921; 23
                4x5
                - Images of two lovers above entrance to village, 1921; 24
                - Maori woman standing beside totem, 1921; 25
                - Typical house in Maori, five people in foreground, four seated and Lowell Thomas standing, 1921; 26
                - Man and woman under cabbage tree, 1921; 27
                - Falls near Wairakei looking downstream, 1921; 28
                - Falls near Wairakei looking upstream, 1921; 29
                - Extinct volcano near Wairakei, 1921; 30
                - Rough sea, 1921; 31
                3x4
                - Lowell Thomas looking into the Dragon’s Mouth, 1921; 32
                - People observing large bird’s nest, Lowell Thomas sitting in nest, 1921; 33
                - People observing a geyser, Lowell Thomas with hands on Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas’s shoulders, 1921; 34
                - Paddle wheel, quiet, 1921; 35
                - Paddle wheel, active, 1921; 36
                - Lowell Thomas looking into the Dragon’s Mouth, 1921; 37
                - Lowell Thomas and others standing on cliff overlooking Champagne Pool, 1921; 38
                - Panorama of Wairakei valley, 1921; 39
                - Panorama of Wairakei valley, Lowell Thomas and William T. Cunningham in foreground, 1921; 40
                - Valley filled with gorse, automobile in distance, 1921; 41
                - Valley filled with gorse, man and woman in horse drawn cart, 1921; 42
                - Close-up of gorse bush, 1921; 43